Most students don't realize that they're stuck until like one month before the deadline when
they realize that they don't know what a Y major essay is supposed to have, what a YR college
essay should have, or how to write essays about how you contribute to your community,
or a lot of the other school-specific prompts. The worst part is that even if
you have a really good Common App essay, if your supplementals are all bland, generic,
and boring, then it's not going to help you get into the colleges that you want to get
into. All of the essays have to be polished, all of them have to be cohesive, and you want
to make sure that each one is actually the best it can be, because otherwise you're harming your
chances of getting into the college that you want to get into. And I see so many students
make the same mistakes over and over on their Y major essays, their Y essay essays. That's
exactly what this package is for. I'm going to break down the whole process for you of how to
get through your supplementals so that you're not left clueless, and so that you know by the
time you click submit on your schools that your supplementals are going to move the needle
in a positive direction for you. I know because I got into every single college that I applied to
$600,000 in merit scholarships, including a full tuition scholarship to Vanderbilt,
and have helped over a thousand students write their college essays and supplementals,
getting them into schools like NYU with full tuition, Penn, Dartmouth, Cornell,
UC Berkeley with a scholarship, Vanderbilt with scholarship, and so many others. And I'm going
to be giving you the same strategies that I've given them to help them write amazing
supplementals. So here's how the calls work. We'll start with your supplemental list and
we'll figure out how many supplementals you have, which prompts repeat, and then come up
with an action plan for how to tackle them during our sessions together. I will start by
helping you with the ones that are going to repeat, like the Y major essays, the YR college
essays, and the community essays. We'll figure out exactly what to do for those because those
will repeat among a lot of the schools. After that point, we'll work on all of your
individual, like school-by-school, unique prompts. I have worked with so many students on
supplementals, so I've seen all of them before, and I know exactly what colleges are looking for
in each of these supplementals. So I will help you come up with unique ideas, figure out how
to structure your essays, how to brainstorm, how to make unique hooks, and we are going to make
sure that every single one of your supplementals is ready to go and looks good by the time you
hit submit. So the package also comes with unlimited email support in between our live
one-on-one calls so that if you have any quick questions about, hey, does this hook look good?
Should I do this topic for my supplemental? That's what I'm here for, and you will have support
so that you're never stuck or guessing on the process. So you can book this package right here
on my website. That being said, if scheduling calls is really difficult for you, I also have an
asynchronous version of this package where I will give you written edits only on your supplementals.
But if you also need help brainstorming, coming up with ideas, and getting more direct
help, that's what these one-on-one calls are for. If you have any questions at all,
feel free to email me, abigaillang at gmail.com,
and you can book right here on this page. I cannot wait to work with you.